Otto Sternoff Beyer Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Subject File, 1905-1947 (Box 9-47)
  - Walsh-Healey Public Contracts Act, circa 1939-1941
  - Washington Social Survey Report, circa 1940-1947
  - Western Electric Co., employee training program
  - Westinghouse Electric and Manufacturing Co., circa 1934-1935
  - Weyerhaeuser Timber Co., circa 1918; 1940-1942
  - Wood Newspaper Machinery Corp., circa 1931
  - Workers Educational Bureau, circa 1927-1933
  - Works Progress Administration, circa 1938-1939 (Box 46)
  - Yeomans Brothers Co.
    - Correspondence, circa 1932-1941
    - Getting new business, circa 1927-1932
    - Minutes of cooperative meetings, circa 1930-1939
    - Protection measurement system, circa 1931
    - Publicity, circa 1930-1932
  - YMCA Commission on Responsible Citizenship, circa 1932-1941 (Box 47)
- General Railroad File, 1915-1948 (Box 48-69)
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports, minutes, notes, charts, articles, printed matter and miscellaneous material relating to Beyer's work regarding railroads.
  - Advisory Committee on Railroad Employment (Box 48)
    - Correspondence, circa 1933-1934
    - Data from Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1932-1933
    - Memoranda
    - Paper by J. Douglas Brown, 1933
    - Preliminary reports
    - Report of the committee
    - Statement by J. B. Eastman
    - Work papers, 1933-1934
  - Alaska Railroad, appointment of Beyer, 1948
  - Aptitude tests for railway workers, circa 1938
  - Association of American Railroads
    - circa 1929-1940
    - Printed releases, circa 1932-1941
  - Association of Western Railways, circa 1936-1939 (Box 49)
  - Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway, circa 1938-1942
  - Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America, circa 1925-1935
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, circa 1924; 1930-1941
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Shopcrafts of America, circa 1937
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, circa 1932-1942
  - Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, circa 1934-1939
  - Carriers agreement, Feb. 1937
  - Central Railroad of New Jersey, circa 1930
  - Central Vermont Railway (Box 50)
    - circa 1928-1933
    - St. Albans Division, cooperative
    - Committee minutes, circa 1936-1937
    - St. Albans Division, Mechanical Department minutes
      - circa 1931-1940
    - Maintenance of way, circa 1931-1932
    - System Committee meetings, circa 1931-1934
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Railway, circa 1924-1931 (Box 51)
  - Chicago and Alton Railway, circa 1931-1935
  - Chicago and Northwestern Railway, cooperative minutes
    - July-Sept. 1925
    - Sept.-Oct. 1925
    - Nov.-Dec. 1925
    - circa 1926-1930
    - circa 1931 (Box 52)
    - General file, circa 1921-1931
  - Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad Co., circa 1934-1940
  - Chicago Great Western Railroad Co., circa 1930-1938
  - Chicago, Indianapolis and Louisville Railroad Co., circa 1930
  - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul Railroad Co., circa 1926-1940
  - Chicago wage agreement, circa 1932
  - Committee on Public Relations, data, circa 1931-1934
  - Company union reports, circa 1933 (Box 53)
  - Company unions in railroads, circa 1930 (Box 54)
  - Competition, circa 1931-1932
  - Consolidations, circa 1930-1932
  - Cooperative policy accomplishments and benefits, Railway Employees Department, circa 1928
  - Court decisions, circa 1929-1937
  - Disputes, circa 1941-1943
  - Economic condition and reorganization plans, circa 1938-1939
  - Employees accidents, costs, circa 1932 (Box 55)
  - Employees Department
    - American Federation of Labor
      - circa 1931-1933
      - circa 1931-1936
      - Memorandum of
    - Proposed survey of accomplishments and benefits of cooperative policy, circa 1928
  - Employees convention
  - Employment trends in the railroad industry, 1934
  - Erie Railroad Co. (Box 56)
    - Cooperative efficiency test of Westinghouse, Cardwell and Triple Spring draft gears
    - Report of rest of friction draft gear
    - Specifications
  - Erie Railway System, circa 1927-1933
  - Express strike, Detroit, Mich., circa 1941
  - Finances, circa 1931
  - Grand Trunk Western Railway (Box 57)
    - Chicago Division, circa 1929-1933
    - Detroit Division, circa 1931-1934
    - Blueprints re mileage and force employed, circa 1922-1926
  - Grand Trunk Western Division, circa 1930-1937
  - Illinois Central System, circa 1932-1942
  - Increase in efficiency, circa 1919
  - Inefficiencies and wastes of American railway operation, circa 1921
  - Integral reorganization of the railroads, circa 1933
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, rulings on Railway Labor Act, circa 1938
  - Labor (Box 58)
    - circa 1931
    - circa 1932
    - circa 1930-1943
  - Labor, circa 1930-1931
  - Labor and reconstruction, circa 1943-1945
  - Labor disputes adjustment, circa 1942-1945
  - Labor organizations, research, circa 1931
  - London, Midland and Scottish Railway Co., circa 1938-1939
  - Louisiana and Arkansas Railroad (Box 59)
    - circa 1933-1938
    - Strike data, circa 1932-1936
  - Mediation, circa 1942
  - Miscellaneous, circa 1926; 1946
  - Missouri Pacific Railroad Co., circa 1941
  - Mobile and Ohio Railroad Co., circa 1933-1934
  - Nashville, Chattanooga and St. Louis Railroad, circa 1935
  - National Railroad Adjustment Board, circa 1936-1941; 1947
  - New Orleans Public Belt Railroad Co., circa 1941
  - New York Central System, circa 1942
  - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Co., circa 1938
  - New York Railroad Club, circa 1937-1938
  - Occupational change, circa 1933
  - Order of Railway Conductors, circa 1939-1940
  - Order of Railroad Telegraphers, circa 1924; 1927-1933
  - Pennsylvania Railroad Co., circa 1936-1940
  - Pere Marquette Railway, circa 1930 (Box 60)
  - Preparatory technical conference on the reduction of hours of work in rail transport, circa 1939
  - Pullman Co., circa 1937-1940
  - Rail and River Coal Co., circa 1932
  - Rail Transport Conference, Geneva, Switzerland
    - circa 1939 See also Oversize
    - Hours of work, 1939
  - Railroad retirement, circa 1938-1939
  - Railway competition, bus and truck, circa 1931-1932
  - Railway Education Bureau, circa 1929-1938
  - Railway Labor Act
    - Amendments, circa 1930-1939
    - Copies of act, circa 1926-1936 (Box 61)
    - Data, circa 1946-1947
    - Drafts of proposed act, circa 1934-1935
    - Emergency Board
      - circa 1937-1939
      - circa 1937-1941
      - circa 1941
      - Complete set of reports, circa 1937-1941
      - Complete set of reports, circa 1937-1941
    - Hearings, circa 1934 (Box 62)
    - Referees file, circa 1939-1941
    - Conference, circa 1929
    - Executives Association, circa 1930-1939
  - Railway labor relations today, circa 1923-1938
  - Railway Labor Research Foundation
    - circa 1929-1934
    - circa 1931
  - Railway labor survey (Box 63)
    - circa 1933
    - Social Science Research Council, circa 1933
  - Railway News and Statistics Bulletin, circa 1931-1934
  - Railway wage levels, 1933
  - Refrigerator Car Lines, labor conditions, circa 1935
  - Reorganization, circa 1933-1935
  - Reports, agreements received, circa 1938-1939
  - Research Service, circa 1938-1939
  - Retirement, circa 1931-1938
  - Royal Commission of Canada, appraisal on behalf of railways, of the commission's report, circa 1932
  - Rutland Railroad, circa 1939-1942 (Box 64)
  - Rutland Railroad Co.
    - Minutes, circa 1940-1942
    - Operating results, circa 1940-1943
  - St. Louis Terminal Railway, circa 1931
  - Scientific management, circa 1919
  - Seaboard Air Line Railway, circa 1931-1937
  - Southern Pacific Railroad, circa 1928-1942
  - Stabilization of employment, circa 1925-1933
  - Statistics, circa 1928
  - Steam locomotives (Box 65)
    - Illinois Central Railway, circa 1916-1917
    - Methods of effecting improvements, circa 1915-1917
    - Tests
      - circa 1913-1916
      - circa 1917-1919; 1932 (Box 66)
  - Survey of the effects of the Depression on railway workers, Advisory Committee, circa 1933
    - Appendix C
    - Appointment of agents, circa 1932-1934
    - General, circa 1933
    - Individuals selected as guides for field investigators, circa 1933 (Box 67)
    - Instructions to agents, circa 1933
    - Miscellaneous data, circa 1932
    - Personnel for field investigators, circa 1933
    - Questionnaires, circa 1933
    - Survey by G. M. Price, circa 1933
    - Financial statements of agents, circa 1932-1934
    - Conclusion, circa 1934
  - Tennessee Railroad Co., circa 1939
  - Texas and Pacific injunction, case R-735, circa 1942
  - Union-management cooperation in the railway industry, circa 1919-1931
  - Union Pacific Railroad Co., circa 1937-1942 (Box 68)
  - United States Railroad Administration
    - circa 1919-1920
    - circa 1920-1926
  - United States railroad
    - Labor Board exhibit on inefficient railroad management, circa 1920
  - Utah-Idaho Central Railroad case, circa 1945-1946
  - Victimization, circa 1934
  - Virginia Railway Co., circa 1936
  - Wage deduction case, circa 1938
  - Wage situation, circa 1920-1946 (Box 69)
  - Wages and freight rate increase, circa 1931-1934
  - Wheeling and Lake Erie Railway Co., circa 1937-1938
  - Work in railroad shops, circa 1933-1938
- Canadian National Railways, 1921-1948 (Box 70-95)
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports, minutes, notes, charts, articles, printed matter, and miscellaneous material relating to the Canadian National Railways.
  - Correspondence (Box 70)
    - 1923-1924
    - 1925
    - 1926
    - 1927
    - 1928
    - 1929 (Box 71)
    - 1930
    - 1930
    - 1931
    - 1931
    - 1931
    - 1932 (Box 72)
    - 1932
    - circa 1933-1940
    - circa 1941-1948
  - Accident records, circa 1932-1943
  - Amalgamation controversy, circa 1931-1938
  - Annual reports, circa 1925-1936; 1942
  - Apprentice training employee education, circa 1927-1939 (Box 73)
  - Canadian Brotherhood of Railway Employees, circa 1928-1930
  - Commercial Telegraphers' Union, circa 1926-1930
  - Car shop performance, comparative statements, circa 1942-1944
  - Cooperative committees
  - Cooperative plan
    - 1931
    - Development, 1923-1928
    - Employee attitude, 1930
    - Five best features, 1931-1932
    - Machinery, 1931-1932 (Box 74)
  - Devices for enlisting
  - Duff Commission
    - Labor's statement to, 1925-1932
    - Report, 1932
  - Equipment, development of, 1926-1943
  - Gains from cooperation, 1926-1927
  - Grievances, 1925
  - History, circa 1931
  - Insurance for sick benefits, 1928-1930
  - Joint cooperative plan, Mechanical Department, constitution governing action and procedure
  - Maintenance of equipment, cooperative program, circa 1929-1936
  - Maintenance of way
    - Annual meetings and reports, MP-CE Section, circa 1943-1947
    - Annual reports, circa 1934-1935
    - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees (Box 75)
    - Brother hood of Maintenance of Way Cooperative
      - Meetings, minutes
        - Allendale Division, circa 1930-1943
        - Atlantic Region
          - General
            - circa 1925-1926
            - circa 1927-1928
            - circa 1929-1944 (Box 76)
          - Car Department
            - circa 1925-1926
            - circa 1927-1929
            - circa 1930-1932
            - circa 1933-1936 (Box 77)
            - circa 1937-1941
          - Motive Power Department
            - circa 1931-1933
            - circa 1934-1941
        - Brandon Division, circa 1930-1933
        - Calgary Division (Box 78)
          - circa 1930-1933
          - circa 1934-1944
        - Campbellton Division, circa 1935-1943
        - Capreol Division, circa 1930-1944 (Box 79)
        - Central Region, circa 1926-1940
        - Charlottetown Division, circa 1930-1939
        - Cochrane Division
          - circa 1930-1941
          - Accident prevention reports, circa 1932-1941 (Box 80)
        - Dauphin Division, circa 1930-1943
        - Duluth, Winnipeg, and Pacific Division, circa 1930-1938
        - Edmonton Division
          - circa 1929-1933
          - circa 1931-1940 (Box 81)
          - circa 1934-1943
        - Edson Division, circa 1930-1933
        - Halifax Division, circa 1930-1940
        - Hornepayne Division, circa 1930-1943 (Box 82)
        - Kamloops Division, circa 1931-1941
        - Laurentain Division, circa 1930-1940
        - Levis Division (Box 83)
          - circa 1930-1935
          - circa 1936-1940
        - London Division
          - circa 1925-1935
          - circa 1936-1940
        - Miscellaneous, circa 1941-1944 (Box 84)
        - Moncton Division (Box 85)
          - circa 1929-1932
          - circa 1933-1936
          - circa 1937-1942
          - circa 1937-1942
        - Montreal Division
        - St. Jerome and St. Lawrence Division Montreal Terminals, circa 1943-1948
        - St. Lawrence Division, Montreal terminals, Montreal Terminals, circa 1930-1943, (5 folders) (Box 86)
        - New Glasgow Division, circa 1932-1941
        - Ottawa Division, circa 1930-1936
        - Port Arthur-Lakehead Division, circa 1930-1938 (Box 87)
        - Portage Division
          - circa 1929-1931
          - circa 1931-1933
        - Portage-Brandon Division, circa 1933-1944
        - Portland Division, circa 1930-1931
        - Prince Albert Division, circa 1930-1942 (Box 88)
        - Saguenay Division, circa 1930-1932
        - St. Thomas Division, circa 1930-1943
        - Saskatoon Division, circa 1930-1940
        - Smithers Division, circa 1930-1937 (Box 89)
        - Stellarton (Nova Scotia) Division, circa 1937-1939
        - Toronto Terminals Division, circa 1930-1933
        - Western Region
          - circa 1930-1933
          - circa 1934-1943
        - Winnipeg Terminal Division, circa 1929-1940 (Box 90)
        - System Cooperative Committee
          - circa 1928-1938
          - circa 1932-1934
          - circa 1939-1947
          - Mechanical Section, circa 1934-1940 (Box 91)
          - MP-CE Section, circa 1942-1947
    - Cooperative program, circa 1930-1933
    - Data
      - circa 1926
      - Undated
      - Undated (Box 92)
    - Department, circa 1927-1941
    - Education and training, circa 1930-1941
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1932
    - Union-management cooperative movement, accident prevention
    - Union membership, circa 1931-1933
  - Motor vehicle competition, circa 1935 (Box 93)
  - Pensions, circa 1923-1930
  - Pictures, 1942-1949
  - Production in repair shops
  - Production measurement system, circa 1928-1942
    - Cost and unit production at principal roundhouses
    - Costs, production and averages
      - circa 1934-1938, (5 folders)
      - circa 1939 (Box 94)
      - circa 1941
  - Production measurement
    - Shop production and costs
      - circa 1931-1942, (8 folders)
    - Unit measurement system
  - Publicity, addresses etc., circa 1935-1939
  - Safety bulletins, circa 1931-1934
  - Safety campaign and accident prevention, circa 1931-1932
  - Safety campaign and posters, circa 1930-1931
  - Stabilization of employment, circa 1928-1931 (Box 95)
  - Statistics, circa 1926-1932
  - Suggestions, circa 1925-1931
  - Survey of shops questionnaire
  - System Federation No. 11, mimeograph releases, cooperative minutes, etc., circa 1929-1940
  - Temiskaming and Northern Ontario Railroad, circa 1928
  - Thornton, Sir Henry
    - General, circa 1931
    - Resignation, circa 1932
    - Statements, circa 1923-1932
  - Union activities, circa 1926-1930
  - Union aid to management, circa 1930
  - Union management cooperation, circa 1925; 1939
  - Wage and employment statistics, circa 1931-1932
  - Wage deduction controversy, circa 1921-1933
  - Wage payment system, report by Beyer, circa 1924
  - Wages, miscellaneous, circa 1933
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company, 1921-1942 (Box 96-105)
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports, minutes, notes, charts, articles, printed matter, and miscellaneous material relating to the Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Co.
  - Agreements, circa 1926-1933 (Box 96)
  - Apprentice training material, circa 1926-1930
  - Buffalo, Rochester and Pittsburgh Railroad, circa 1932-1942
  - Cooperative plan
    - Committee, circa 1924-1928
    - Cumulated suggestions, circa 1924-1929
    - Development
      - circa 1924
      - circa 1921-1928 (Box 97)
    - Machinery, circa 1921-1931
    - Minutes, Glenwood
      - circa 1924-1930, (4 folders)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 98)
      - circa 1930
      - circa 1931, (2 folders)
    - Policy introduction to maintenance of way, circa 1928-1931
    - Policy maintenance of way, circa 1930-1931
    - Summary of suggestions
      - circa 1924-1928
      - circa 1927-1930 (Box 99)
      - circa 1928-1931
      - circa 1931-1938
  - Employment stabilization
    - circa 1923-1929, (5 folders)
    - circa 1930-1932, (3 folders) (Box 100)
    - Miscellaneous
  - Engine failure performance
    - circa Feb.-June, 1932
    - circa July, 1931-1932
  - Engine No. 1003
  - Financial statements, circa 1932-1941
  - Forces, hours (thirty-hour week), etc., circa 1923-1933
  - Glenwood shops, circa 1923-1924 (Box 101)
  - Grievances, circa 1931
  - Locomotive inspection
    - circa 1924-1932
    - All lines, circa 1926, 1941
    - Eastern lines, circa 1927-1932
  - Miscellaneous, circa 1927-1928 (Box 102)
  - Old age pensions, circa 1930-1931
  - Overtime, circa 1923-1928
  - Posters, circa 1929-1931
  - Printing plant organization, circa 1930-1931
  - Publicity, circa 1931-1938
  - Reconstruction Finance Corp., work loan data, circa 1927-1942
  - Rules of service, circa 1928-1930
  - Rules changes, circa 1923-1929
  - Safety campaigns, circa 1924-1928
  - Safety Flashes, circa 1932-1941
  - Seniority, miscellaneous, circa 1927-1932 (Box 103)
  - Shop improvement program, circa 1923-1924
  - Statistics, circa 1924-1930
  - System cooperative meetings, minutes
    - circa 1924-1927
    - circa 1925-1929
    - circa 1928-1938
  - System Federation No. 30
    - circa 1925-1933
    - Cooperative agreement, circa 1931 (Box 104)
    - Cooperative Committee minutes, circa 1931
    - Organization, circa 1924-1931
  - Unemployment relief
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1931-1932
    - Reports, circa 1931-1932
  - Union gains from cooperation, circa 1923-1931
  - Union-management cooperation
    - circa 1925-1928
    - Plan, circa 1925
  - Union membership, shop crafts, circa 1924-1932
  - Wage increases, circa 1923-1929 (Box 105)
  - Willard, Daniel
    - circa 1923-1929
    - Statements, circa 1923-1931
    - List of speeches, 1910-1929
- Tennessee Valley Authority, 1933-1948 (Box 106-112)
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports, minutes, notes, charts, articles, printed matter, and miscellaneous material relating to the Tennessee Valley Authority.
  Arranged alphabetically by topic, organization, or type of material, with the exception that speeches and articles by others are organized out of sequence at the end of the series.
  - Correspondence
    - Clapp, Gordon R. (Box 106)
      - circa 1935-1939
      - circa 1940-1942
    - Gant, George, circa 1942-1944
    - Jandrey, A. S., circa 1940-1941
    - Lilienthal, David E., circa 1936-1941
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1935-1941
    - Shultz, E. B., circa 1941
  - Administrative codes, circa 1939-1942
  - Apprenticeship Council, circa 1939-1941
  - Board of Adjustment, referees, circa 1940
  - Employee relationship policy, circa 1934-1945 (Box 107)
  - Employee conditions, circa 1936-1943
  - Freight rate issue, circa 1943
  - Grievances
    - Labor-Management Conference regarding case of W. E. Blanton and Douglas Parker, Nov. 1940
    - Procedure for settling plant grievances, circa 1942-1945
    - Statement re discharge of A. R. Dean and C. R. Seaton
  - Joint cooperative committees
    - Committee meetings, circa 1940-1944
    - Minutes
      - circa 1943-1944
      - circa 1945-1948, (5 folders) (Box 108)
      - circa 1948 (Box 109)
    - Program and achievements, circa 1941-1946
    - Labor-management relations
      - Agreements of 1940
      - Board-council meeting, 16 May 1944
      - Proposed plans, circa 1944
      - Work papers, circa 1931; 1937-1940
  - Legislation, proposed, circa 1933-1941 (Box 110)
  - Miscellaneous
  - Publicity
    - Magazine, circa 1935-1944
    - Newspaper clippings, circa 1935-1938
  - Teamwork, circa 1943-1948
  - Tennessee Electric v. TVA, circa 1938
  - Training plans
    - circa 1936-1938
    - circa 1939-1941
    - circa 1942-1945
  - Wage adjustments, circa 1936-1945
  - Wage conferences, circa 1939; 1945-1947
  - Wage and jurisdictional disputes, circa 1936-1939 (Box 111)
  - War Manpower Commission, relations with, circa 1943
  - Waterway transportation, circa 1943-1945
  - Speeches and articles about TVA, 1935-1947 (Box 112)
- Bonneville Power Administration, 1940-1947 (Box 113-114)
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports, minutes, notes, charts, articles, printed matter, and miscellaneous material relating to the Bonneville Power Administration.
  - Administrative orders, circa 1940-1943 (Box 113)
  - Construction policies, circa 1945
  - Collective agreement between administrator and Columbia Power Trades Council, circa 1945-1947
  - Labor agreement, circa 1945-1947
  - Legislation, circa 1940-1945
  - Maps, Bonneville area, circa 1941-1946
  - Reports, circa 1941-1945 (Box 114)
  - Sweden, "State Controlled Companies in Sweden," circa 1943
  - Wage conference, circa 1945-1946
  - Wage and employee information, circa 1946-1947
- Speech and Article File, 1919-1947 (Box 115-124)
  Correspondence and texts of speeches and articles by Beyer, including drafts and printed and near print copies. Arranged according to type of material and chronologically therein, with the exception of Beyer's draft history of railroad personnel located at the end of the series.
  - Correspondence, 1923-1947, (21 folders) (Box 115)
  - Texts (Box 116)
    - 1919, Mar. "Efficiency Through Democracy in Railway Industry of America"
    - 1923, Oct. "Employee Morale Problem of Our Railroads"
    - 1924
      - Apr.
        - "Business Policy," Harvard Business School, Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
        - Policy Holders Service Bureau, Metropolitan Life Co.
      - Nov. "A Constructive Program for the Federated Railway Men of Canada"
    - 1925
      - Feb. "Citizenship of Industry"
      - Aug. "Railroad Union-Management Cooperation"
    - 1926, June
      - "The Cooperative Policy of the Railway Employees Department"
      - "The Value of the Railway Shopman to His Industry"
    - 1927
      - Feb., National Civic Federation luncheon remarks
      - June, Railway Employees Department Convention
      - Sept., "Labor's Contribution to the Scientific Organization of the Industry"
      - Dec., Industrial Seminar, Congregational Churches
    - 1928
      - May
        - Baltimore and Ohio System Federation Convention
        - "Labor's Constructive Function in the Railway Industry"
      - Oct.
        - "Experiences with Cooperation Between Labor and Management in the Railway Industry"
    - 1929
      - Mar., "Sources of Potential Leaders in Industry"
      - Apr., Review of Human Relations in Railroading
      - June, Baltimore and Ohio Plan of Cooperation
    - 1930, Dec.
      - "Union-Management Competes and Wins"
      - "That Acid Test, The Ledger Indicates Success"
    - 1931, Mar.
      - "Keeping at the Job"
      - "Steady Work Through Cooperation"
    - 1932
      - Apr., "Constructive Human Relations in the Railway Industry"
      - May, "Labor's Contribution to Democratic Influences in Industry"
      - July, "Labor-Management Cooperation"
    - 1933 (Box 117)
      - Feb., "An Industrial Policy for America"
      - Mar., Articles regarding Secretary of Labor Frances Perkins
      - Aug., "Unemployment and the Morale of Industry"
    - 1934 Nov., Brotherhood of Clerks Convention